<resources>
    <!-- Title for the application. [CHAR LIMIT=12] -->
    <string name="app_name">Xanthi Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- Top intro text -->
    <string name="intro_text_top"><b>Xanthi...</b></string>
    <!-- Image text description -->
    <string name="intro_image_text_description">Photo of Xanthi</string>
    <!-- Bottom intro text -->
    <string name="intro_text_bottom"><b>...tour guide!!</b></string>

    <!-- Tab names -->
    <string name="tab_attraction">Attractions</string>
    <string name="tab_monuments">Feasts</string>
    <string name="tab_food">Food</string>
    <string name="tab_night_life">Night Life</string>

    <!-- SITES -->

        <!-- Sites text of titles -->
        <string name="site_old_town_title">Old Town of Xanthi</string>
        <string name="site_clock_tower_title">Clock Tower</string>
        <string name="site_municipal_art_gallery_title">Municipal Art Gallery</string>
        <string name="site_kosinthos_river_title">Kosinthos River</string>
        <string name="site_nestos_river_title">Nestos River</string>

        <!-- Sites text of descriptions -->
        <string name="site_old_town_description">
            Old town of Xanthi was built in 1829 after an earthquake that destroyed the older town. It
            is located at the north of the city and it keeps the old style of the buildings till nowadays.
        </string>
        <string name="site_clock_description">
            Clock Tower is the symbol of the Xanthi city. It is located at the center plaza and stands
            there for ages.
        </string>
        <string name="site_municipal_art_gallery_description">
            Municipal Art Gallery is located at the centre of the old town in an impressive mansion.
            Free admission is an advantage for someone who may want to visit and get some knowledge
            about the history of Xanthi.
        </string>
        <string name="site_kosinthos_river_description">
            Kosinthos river is the river that passes through the city of Xanthi. His geographical place
            with all the old bridges make him a very nice play to visit.
        </string>
        <string name="site_nestos_river_description">
            Nestos river is the biggest river that passes through Thrace. It is located near Xanthi city
            and attracts many wild species of birds and wolfs. It is worth to visit with organized
            "extreme adventure" groups.
        </string>

    <!-- FEASTS -->

        <!-- Feasts text of titles -->
        <string name="feasts_of_carnival_title">Carnival</string>
        <string name="feasts_0f_old_town_title">Clock Tower</string>
        <string name="feasts_of_youth_title">Municipal Art Gallery</string>

        <!-- Sites text of descriptions -->
        <string name="feasts_of_carnival_description">
            The carnival of Xanthi is the second biggest carnival parade in Greece after that one of
            Patras. All the people of the nearby cities gather to celebrate and burn the Joker in
            order to seal the end of the feast.
        </string>
        <string name="feasts_of_old_town_description">
            The feast of old Town takes place at the old city. All the dancing organizations of Xanthi
            take part and dance the traditional dances in order to celebrate the liberty of the city
            from the second world war.
        </string>
        <string name="feasts_of_youth_description">
            The feasts of youth are help in the main plaza of Xanthi. There the youth musical band of
            the musical school of Xanthi sings songs of the Greek music artist "Manos Hatzidakis" in
            order to salute his actions and the Greek rebellion.
        </string>

    <!-- Cost strings -->
    <string name="low_cost">€ -> €€</string>
    <string name="high_cost">€€ -> €€€</string>

    <!-- Food -->

        <!-- Feasts text of titles -->
        <string name="food_palaia_poli_title">Palia Poli</string>
        <string name="food_to_pilima_title">To Pilima</string>
        <string name="food_to_vareli_title">To Vareli</string>
        <string name="food_nea_ellas_title">Nea Ellas</string>
        <string name="food_papaparaskevas_title">Papaparaskevas</string>

        <!-- Sites text of descriptions -->
        <string name="food_palaia_poli_description">
            "Palaia poli" is the most know tavern of Xanthi city. Very good quality of traditional Greek
            and Turkish food. Very nice and friendly service. It is well know for the kebab food.
        </string>
        <string name="food_to_pilima_description">
            "To Pilima" is a tavern outside of the Xanthi city. Easy to find and very good quality of
            food. It has a variety of foods but it is very fabled for the wild animals that they hunt
            and cook extremely good.
        </string>
        <string name="food_to_vareli_description">
            "To Vareli" is one tavern inside the old town of Xanthi city. It is considered one of the
            most "in" and quality (concerning the food) places around the city. Best known for the
            steaks they serve.
        </string>
        <string name="food_nea_ellas_description">
            "Nea Ellas" is a traditional patisserie shop widely know around whole Greece. The sweets
            they produce are from the tradition of Greece and Turkey and are very tasty as they are
            created with biological ingredients.
        </string>
        <string name="food_papaparaskevas_description">
            "Papaparaskevas" is also one of the most well known patisseries around Greece. The famous
            "kariokes" is a must to taste. Also, "Papaparaskevas" is very well known for the chocolate
            sweets they sell.
        </string>

    <!-- Night Life -->

        <!-- Night Life texts of titles -->
        <string name="night_life_kivernio_title">Kivernio</string>
        <string name="night_life_my_club_title">My Club</string>
        <string name="night_life_dili_dili_title">Dili Dili</string>
        <string name="night_life_Chokolata_title">Sokolata</string>

        <!-- Night Life texts of descriptions -->
        <string name="night_life_kivernio_description">
            "Kivernio" is the most know and populated bar-cafe-club of Xanthi city. Mostly visited by
            students of the university, but its style is friendly for all ages. Located at the center
            of the city is a must visit place.
        </string>
        <string name="night_life_my_club_description">
            "My Club" is the biggest club of all Thrace. It only opens at summer but the events it
            hosts are very crouded and with a finesse. If you visit Xanthi at the end of the summer
            you surely must spend a night there.
        </string>
        <string name="night_life_dili_dili_description">
            "Dili dili" is one of the most beautiful traditional cafes of Xanthi city. Located at the
            center of old town offers an old stylish coffee brake for all. It is considered one of the
            best neo-classical coffee shops of the city.
        </string>
        <string name="night_life_Chokolata_description">
            "Chocolata" caffee is a nice winter coffee-tea shop. It has a large variety of teas, liquid
            chocolates and liqueurs. A very warm, friendly and classic place to visit the winter to
            get warmer and chat with friends.
        </string>

</resources>